Thank you for watching
me
no minaga!
Aaaaahhh!
Celebrating its 11th anniversary, Nokizaka46 now has more than 250 songs, so this time, Bananaman and Nokizaka46 members had a grueling showdown in the "Criz Project," in which they took a variety of angles of their songs and showed their answers to the audience.
Last time, both Nimura and Himura outwitted the other members with their answers.
The official big brother Daiken and
Tonight's finalists will win the title of Song Master Eikan, the person who understands the song the best!
Next up is the Nokizaka Variety Intro!
No but Variety
The intro quiz that has been a great battle up to now will be presented in various forms.
Earn 3 points for each correct answer in a quick-push format without any help!
Bananaman will sing at the court dame.
We'll start with the normal intro first.
Let's get started!
Nogitaka Song Master
Saku-chan
Wow!
Well, if I can do it someday, I can do it today
I made a mistake.
Can't make a mistake or can't make a mistake?
Yuna please
Running away from the water
Running water!
It's "running away water" now.
It's "Tenteleren".
Wait a minute... this is amazing... when you make a mistake, it's like a piranha bait chicken.
I don't think I'm going to make a mistake, so I'm just like, "Oh, he's gone, I can't catch him.
I can't believe I made a mistake.
I'm scared.
And now for the next question.
Nagitaka Songmaster
Oh, no.
I did it! Jumping joker flash!
I did it! I'm strong!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
I know, I know.
I'm trying to push it, but I'm losing.
I'm really losing.
Let's get on with it.
Right card, song master.
Mencar.
Wait, the title doesn't come up.
It's got to be Menker's title.
Correct.
Natsuki Loneliness Brothers
I know... I know... but it doesn't shine
What's this?
Why doesn't it shine?
But it's a pattern of not coming out in a hurry.
Okay, let's go.
Akisaka Soumu Master
He's singing.
"Terererereren, dererereren, dererereren, dererereren, dererereren.
Yes, you're right.
A little more, please.
The one that says "Tererereren, derereren, dererereren, dererereren, dererereren, dererereren".
Like this...
That's how they sing it, right?
Teren-ren, de-ren-ren de-ren-ren, de-ren-ren de-ren-ren
Terenren de deren deren deren deren
It's a little more like a chorus.
Sabi sabi sabi sabi
Terenren
That's pretty dramatic, isn't it?
zenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzenzen
I can't get the song out.
What about this?
This is out.
I want some more of this.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Terereren, derereren, derereren, derereren, derereren.
And I got something else.
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming
One more thing.
Um, um...
Let's see...
Everybody be quiet.
I'm trying to be quiet.
Who's quiet?
No, who?
Quiet.
Who?
Not Westfield?
That's out.
No, it's not.
Yuna-chan, please. You promised.
That's it.
That's right, I like her.
What kind?
That's it.
See? It fits.
But Nanase, it's not a fold.
But you're getting married.
You were right after you said that.
Well... Wakatsuki... Akimoto...
I guess Denderen isn't good enough.
I should've sung it one more time.I wish I could have sung it one more time.
It was kind of close.
Can I try one of mine? Here.
Is this for real? This one.
Doesn't it stick?
It does. Thank you very much.
It's gonna work.
I'm sure there's someone out there who does, but it's all connected.
Let's go.
Nogizaka Song Master.
Oh!
You haven't heard.
No, I haven't.
I don't know.
This is fine, you and me.
I'll give it to you.
We did this at the last show.
You did it with Ume, right?
Yes, please.
You were doing the Ume thing, right?
Wearing fancy clothes.
"Pang, pang, pang, pang, pang." Tropical stuff.
For example.
For example, right?
Because of what?
You know...
Maybe it's the other one.
I'll ask you one more time.
No, sir.
Oh!
A human being, a kid. Correct.
Yeah, but you're right. I didn't do that one.
I didn't do that one... that one... that one... that one... that one... that one...
I must've got it mixed up with that one.
I can't get it, Mr. Himuro.
Next, a quiz to cut out the lyrics.
Listen to just one word of a song and guess what it's about.
First, we'll play the lyrics of the song "World World World.
The lyrics will be played and you'll have to guess which song it is.
Let's hear it for the Nogizaka Song Master!
Oh, Mr. Nogi, the loneliest love in the world is...
No, it's a new world.
What is it?
Akaki
Actuaries
Correct.
Yay! Actuaries.
So you're an actuary... because we're linked.
She's losing it.
I'm telling you, it's definitely connected.
I'm so sorry.
That's too bad.
This is a tough one, because you have to go back and forth between the decades.
I'm going to go full speed around the world for one more question.
Let's go.
Nagisaka Song Master
Correct.
Yan-chan, go ahead.
Sing out
Correct.
See, I told you they're definitely connected.
You did it!
You did it.
Don't lose
Lyric Clipping Quiz
The next subject is the future
Let's get to it!
Nogizaka Talk Master
Yang-chan.
Oh, it stopped.
Sing out
Sakira
I'm tempted to take the long way home
Ew.
That's amazing... once this starts again, I'll never make it.
You're right.
I can't listen to it a second time.
It's unnatural.
Let's continue with Mirai!
Morisaka Song Master
Mirai.
What was that?
Mirai de...
What's that?
In Mirai
I've never heard of it.
What's this? I want to be on TV.
Mirai de
I've never heard of it.
I've heard of this... because Mistur is listening to it right now.
In Mirai
TOMORROW'S MAN O'S
Tomorrow's Man O's.
Why are you playing "Tomorrow's Man O's"?
No, it's Morisaka's song.
I've heard it before.
Shall we hear it a second time?
He said...
I put my hand on it, and he said...I put my hand on the window and you said...
What was that thing you said, the thing that opens the window?
I got that one wrong.
Like a Mirai egg.
The one you got wrong is not Mirai.
It's not Mirai.
The one with the open window.
The window was open, and the egg was Mirai.
I'm picking up the Mirai.
I have too many memories of this show.
Shall we play it again?
Let's do it again.
Okay, here we go.
Now the song.
It means good-bye, Ibiki-chan.
Correct.
Where is it?
Beyond the lyrics, everyone in the city far away
This future
Difficult
Maybe it was.
Let's continue, shall we?
Which car is it?
The car.
Let's get to it.
Nogizaka Soul Monster
Ona-chan
Rewind Day
Correct answer
Wow!
I hope it was easy to understand.
One more question, and we'll be right back.
Tanaka Song Master
Oh! Zel-chan.
Listen to the car engine.
Name the song.
I'm a member
Disagree
Yumiinki
House
awesome
great!
I got it right.
A little hint of sound.
Ah, here we are.
That was one hell of a car.
Oh, man.
I knew Yumiki was here.
Yumiki's making a lot of money.
Yay!
She's catching up!
Now it's time for the slow playback quiz!
A part of the chorus of a certain song is played in slow motion, and those who know what song it is are asked to guess the chorus.
If you know what song it is, just press the button and it'll play the chorus.
Let's go!
Fujizaka Dragonfly Master
Oh, really?
Yuna, you can do it today because you can do it someday.
This might be difficult.
You're so slow.
Let's hear it again.
Here it is.
What's your name?
Too bad. I'd like to hear a little more.
Let's go again.
Yuna-chan.
When the spring dion blooms.
Correct answer
Almost now
I see.
I see... I see... I see...
It's like this.
Let's continue with the slow intro.
Green Soapenbuster
The protective color of happiness
Wow!
I had no idea.
How did you know?
Well then, let's go!
Oda is the application master.
Seira-chan.
Route 246.
I'm afraid not.
Let's hear it again.
Two, three.
I have no idea.
Yumiki.
Wait, Ringer?
Ringer?
You made it.
Thank you.
Kakkin.
Secret Graffiti
Wow!
I did it!
This is super hard!
The amount of food is 100 pieces!
The difficulty level has increased and the members are finally coming into their own!The difficulty level has increased and the members are finally showing their true colors.
Bananaman was in a big pinch, and here comes the double playback quiz!
Two songs will be played at the same time, so if you know both songs, please answer the questions by pressing the button as fast as you can.
If you don't know both songs, you can't answer correctly.
All right.
Let's go!
Nogizaka Song Master
Let's hear your memories.
What's one?
Ride that bike.
Burst of memories?
Burst of memories.
You can say it, can't you?
Okay.
Victory.
You fought well.
I didn't hear the burst of memories.
I didn't.
Bike.
All right!
All right.
Let's go one more question.
YASAKA Song Master
How did it start?
One more.
One more, right?
I only heard "triggers".
Kikkou and
Your name is hope
Correct.
Trigger and
Full Enso
Yes!
Yamashita's strong.
I heard that.
But...
He's strong.
I only heard one song.
It's hard to hear four different ones.
One more question.
YASAKA SONGMASTER
Mr. Yasaka, nothing.
I only understand one of them.
How many times have I heard "blue sky"?
What?
One.
Saku-chan
How many times have you wondered about the blue sky and under?
Wow!
That's great.
What?
Oh, really?
That's amazing.
That's awesome.
But you're gonna be better than that.
All right, I'll be right back.
I'd like to answer that question.
Impossible song master
Yes, Yuki.
Every day is a brand new day
And one more thing
Oh no, what to do, what to do, what to do
Is he a good guy?
Girls rule
Correct answer
Here's a quiz to see how fast you can turn the chorus of a song.
The chorus of a certain song
It is played at 3 times speed.
If you know what song it is, press the button to answer.
Yes, and a part of it.
Let's go!
Nogizaka Song Master
No, seriously, I get it.
You figured it out?
The world's loneliest rubber
What?
How did you know?
Oh, my God!
Seriously, where is the loneliest rubber in the world?
Oh, my God.
There it is.
Oh, my God, from the beginning.
The way it goes up and down.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy.
Let's go to the second question!
Fujisaka Soul Master
What a lie!
Romance Told in Advance
What?
That's strong!
You're good at quick quizzes!
That's great!
How come I can't hear you?
Let's try it again with the speed.
Nagisa or Tome MasterNagisa or Tome Master
It's stuck.
Are you okay?
New count.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's too hard.
Let's hear it again.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, Yumiki!
Friday the 13th.
Oh, really?
That's amazing.
I have no idea.
Playback in reverse
Next is the reverse quiz!
Play the chorus of a song in reverse
Let's go to the first question!
Nogizaka Song Master
Nogizaka Song Master Quiz
Play the chorus of a song in reverse
Oh!
Ume
Fan
Correct answer
That's great.
I don't know why.
That's weird.
Let's play another question backwards.
Kaoru Nakamura
Song master
Correct answer
Ume
Sun Knock
Correct answer
You're good at it.
Why are you so good at this?
Oh, my God.
Wrong answer and reverse playback intro.
Umezawa's threat to catch up with the winner in a huge uphill battle!
The last of the intro block was the most difficult quiz, the triple playback quiz!
Can you distinguish three songs played at the same time?
Please answer the question. Let's go!
Nogizaka Song Master
Oh! Oh! No! No!
Only two songs.
I love you, way back.
One more.
Oh, no! Gurkha.
Sorry.
Mr. Bottom.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
That's a group car, right?
I didn't mean "the group" as in "the group".
I made a mistake.
You might be able to tell if you listen to the second half. Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
That's it. That's it.
I love you.
That's what you call love.
That's what I keep hearing.
I'll pay you back.
Not even close.
I hear "I love you" when I'm on my way home.
What's one more?
I'm sorry
Yanchan
I love you - the way home makes me want to stay
Take off your uniform and say goodbye
Correct
What?
There it is.
That's right.
I think if you listen to it when you know the answer, you'll hear it.
Let's hear it.
Oh, this sense of style
Where is it?
What is this sense of taste?
No, it's too hard. Three songs are too hard.
Let's try one more.
Let's go!
Nogizaka Song Master
I don't get it.
I like "Baisikiru" (Run, Baisikiru)
No, you don't.
Ume.
There it is... the arms and legs are too long.
I'm sorry, I'm not fast enough.
Let's hear it one more time.
I like to pretend it's summer.
What?
That's right.
Yumiki...
Um... I like you, Natsufuri... from Mr. Kubo's "Rescue".
My rescue
Kubo-san's rescueKubo's Rescue
That's our way of answering the question.
Kubo-san to the rescue!
Let's try it, Yanchan!
I like to pretend I'm in the summer.
Wow, that's good!
Amazing!
No, this is good!
This is the end of the intro quiz block.
With Umezawa's consecutive correct answers and Kanagawa's hot pursuit
The battle for the top spot was very close!
And finally, the last quiz was the same as the last time, but with two clues.
The last question was the same as the last time, two clues quiz.
The first clue of the first question of the final was the expression on Kubo's face.
What?
It's innocent.
Cute, but just cute.
It's hard to find.
What's with the kiss?
No, no, no. Plum.
No, no, no...
No, it's not.
Midsummer
Bandaid Gokisei's
No, sir.
I saw them.
It's all a peach of a dream.
No, sir.
So this is it?
This one's tough.
How often do they do quizzes like this on TV?
If you think about it, it's quite difficult.
The correct answer is not given by the expression on the face.
Next is an illustration of Hayashi.
How about "Hayashi"?
It's a wave.
Wave.
Then, please give us a hint.
This one.
I think it's easy to understand.
Yes, thank you.
Yacht.
Amazing.
That's right.
Correct. I read that.
What do you mean, "Gurkha" with that expression? It's the very innocence and purity of Ikoma's early look, with the upturned eyes.
She did have that kind of mouth. She looked like Ikoma.
Bananaman's team, Citarra's fine play made up for the delay in the introduction.
And now, the final question. The first clue is the first clue.
The first clue is an English word.
I'll have Tamami say it for me. I can get it.
Sakaguchi came up with the English word based on the image of the song...
Yami!
I got it! That's amazing!
Bananaman's team takes the fastest time again. Can they get the right answer with just one clue?
Yami
Yay, I got it!
Three-colored bread!
Yes!
You got it!
That's great!
That's really great.
That's great.
This is fast.
Yay!
How did you know?
There aren't many food songs.
You just thought of a ring with a squid roast.
That's amazing!
The first Ogisaka song mastermind who won the heated competition
He'll go down with Bananaman with 31 points.
We did it!
We're the Ogisaka Songmasters!
Congratulations!
We did it!
I think I'll put out a Mercury or something.
Yamashita came in second, by the way.
Last place... last place...
I'm actually getting Delenderen and others, too.
Kubo and the others must have joined as players.
If you do, you'll get it for sure.
No, no, it's impossible.
Manatsu Akimoto and the Legend
Next Episode
Instant Channel Subscription Song
Seino
Subscribe to our channel!
Please give us a high rating and comment!
Bye bye!